<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Agent</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Agent</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Large Language Models&#39; Function Calling via Self-Refinement Multiscale Loss and Automated Data Refinement</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;funreason-enhancing-large-language-models-function-calling-via-self-refinement-multiscale-loss-and-automated-data-refinement&#34;&gt;FunReason: Enhancing Large Language Models&amp;rsquo; Function Calling via Self-Refinement Multiscale Loss and Automated Data Refinement&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Function call becomes a fundamental concept in Large Language Models, enabling more efficient interaction.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We propose FunReason, FunReason enhances LLMs&amp;rsquo; function calling by balancing reasoning and execution accuracy. Using automated data refinement and Self-Refinement Multiscale Loss (SRML), it generates high-quality training data for query parseability, reasoning coherence, and precise function calls. SRML optimizes both aspects during training, matching GPT-4o performance while minimizing forgetting.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter VI: Esmeralda</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/chapter-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/chapter-6/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are delighted to be able to inform the reader, that during the whole of&#xA;this scene, Gringoire and his piece had stood firm. His actors, spurred on&#xA;by him, had not ceased to spout his comedy, and he had not ceased to&#xA;listen to it. He had made up his mind about the tumult, and was determined&#xA;to proceed to the end, not giving up the hope of a return of attention on&#xA;the part of the public. This gleam of hope acquired fresh life, when he&#xA;saw Quasimodo, Coppenole, and the deafening escort of the pope of the&#xA;procession of fools quit the hall amid great uproar. The throng rushed&#xA;eagerly after them. “Good,” he said to himself, “there go all the&#xA;mischief-makers.” Unfortunately, all the mischief-makers constituted the&#xA;entire audience. In the twinkling of an eye, the grand hall was empty.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter V: Quasimodo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/chapter-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/chapter-5/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the twinkling of an eye, all was ready to execute Coppenole’s idea. Bourgeois, scholars and law clerks all set to work. The little chapel situated opposite the marble table was selected for the scene of the grinning match. A pane broken in the pretty rose window above the door, left free a circle of stone through which it was agreed that the competitors should thrust their heads. In order to reach it, it was only necessary to mount upon a couple of hogsheads, which had been produced from I know not where, and perched one upon the other, after a fashion. It was settled that each candidate, man or woman (for it was possible to choose a female pope), should, for the sake of leaving the impression of his grimace fresh and complete, cover his face and remain concealed in the chapel until the moment of his appearance. In less than an instant, the chapel was crowded with competitors, upon whom the door was then closed.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter IV: Master Jacques Coppenole</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/chapter-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/chapter-4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;While the pensioner of Ghent and his eminence were exchanging very low&#xA;bows and a few words in voices still lower, a man of lofty stature, with a&#xA;large face and broad shoulders, presented himself, in order to enter&#xA;abreast with Guillaume Rym; one would have pronounced him a bull-dog by&#xA;the side of a fox. His felt doublet and leather jerkin made a spot on the&#xA;velvet and silk which surrounded him. Presuming that he was some groom who&#xA;had stolen in, the usher stopped him.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter III: Monsieur the Cardinal</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 11:13:32 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Poor Gringoire! the din of all the great double petards of the Saint-Jean,&#xA;the discharge of twenty arquebuses on supports, the detonation of that&#xA;famous serpentine of the Tower of Billy, which, during the siege of Paris,&#xA;on Sunday, the twenty-sixth of September, 1465, killed seven Burgundians&#xA;at one blow, the explosion of all the powder stored at the gate of the&#xA;Temple, would have rent his ears less rudely at that solemn and dramatic&#xA;moment, than these few words, which fell from the lips of the usher, “His&#xA;eminence, Monseigneur the Cardinal de Bourbon.”&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
